In this video, we're going to wrap up our discussion of Java by taking a look at a
在本视频中，我们将通过查看一个
couple of additional topics and how they are integrated into the language design.
几个附加主题，以及它们如何集成到语言设计中。
Consistent with Java's dynamic nature Java allows classes to be loaded at runtime.
与Java的动态特性一致，Java允许在运行时加载类。
But this means that you can actually add functionality to an executing Java program
但这意味着您实际上可以向正在执行的Java程序添加功能
so, while it's running, by loading a new class. And this creates potential issues
所以，当它运行时，通过加载一个新类。这就产生了潜在的问题
with type safety and security because now there is a distinction between compiled
类型安全和安全性，因为现在编译的
time and load time. So, type checking of the source takes place at compile time and
时间和加载时间。因此，源代码的类型检查在编译时进行，并且
this is the kind of type checking we discussed in earlier in earlier videos.
这就是我们在前面的视频中讨论的类型检查。
But the, the loader, when you actually go to load a class, you're loading bytecode,
但是，装载器，当你真正去装入一个类的时候，你正在装入字节码，
you're not loading source and it's not being type checked again. And it could be,
您没有加载源文件，也没有再次进行类型检查。也有可能是，
that this bytecode didn't come, you know, from a trusted source. This bytecode might
这个字节码不是来自一个可信的来源。此字节码可能
not be the output of a compiler that did type checking, before it produced the
不是执行类型检查的编译器的输出，在它生成
bytecode. So, the bytecode might not actually satisfy the type assumptions of
字节码。因此，字节码实际上可能不满足
the Java implementation. So essentially, we have to check the bytecode again. And
Java实现。所以本质上，我们必须再次检查字节码。和
a, and a procedure called bytecode verification takes place when the class is
A，一个称为字节码验证的过程在类被
loaded, alright. And, and byte code verification is really a type checking of
装好了，好的。并且，字节码验证实际上是一种类型检查
bytecode. That's, that's essentially what it does. The procedure is a little bit
字节码。这就是它本质上的作用。这个过程有一点
different because we don't have you know, the code here is much lower level and so
不同之处在于我们没有，这里的代码级别要低得多，所以
the algorithms look a little bit different. But what they're really doing
算法看起来有点不同。但他们真正在做的是
is type checking the, thebytecode. So, now the loading policies are handled by
是类型检查，字节码。因此，现在加载策略由
something called the class loader. And the class loader is a special class in Java
一种叫做类加载器的东西。而类加载器是Java中的一个特殊类
and it decides what classes can be loaded and actually early on in Java, a bunch of
它决定了哪些类可以加载，实际上在Java的早期，有一堆
security problems were discovered. Aware an attacker could get control of the class
发现了安全问题。意识到攻击者可能会控制类
loader install it's own class loader that would be much more permissive than the
加载器安装它自己的类加载器，这将比
Java standard class loader and subve rt the system. But those issues were fixed
Java标准类加载器和Subve RT系统。但是这些问题已经解决了
quite awhile ago, alright. And another interesting thing about Java is that the
很久以前了，好吧。关于Java的另一件有趣的事情是
classes may also be unloaded. So, you don't, you can not, not only load classes,
也可以卸载类。所以，你不能，你不能，不仅装入类，
you can also unload classes. And the last time I checked this was not particularly
您还可以卸载类。我最后一次检查这个并不是特别的
well specified in the definition and so it's a little bit unclear exactly what it
在定义中有很好的说明，所以它的确切含义是什么还不是很清楚
meant when you unloaded the class and what happened to all the existing objects, for
意味着当您卸载类以及所有现有对象发生的情况时，
example, of that class. Now, I'd like to spend a few minutes talking about
例如，那个班级的。现在，我想花几分钟谈谈
initialization in Java, which is quite complex, and this shouldn't be too much of
Java中的初始化，这相当复杂，这应该不会太多
a surprise because if you remember initialization in COOL was also pretty
令人惊讶的是，如果您还记得Cool中的初始化也很漂亮
complex and Java is just a superset of COOL so it has all the initialization
复杂，而Java只是COOL的超集，所以它有所有的初始化
issues that COOL has plus much more. And now the main source of complication is
酷的问题加上更多。现在并发症的主要来源是
concurrency but other language features also add to the complexity of
并发性，但其他语言功能也增加了
initialization in Java. And, in fact you could do worse. If you want to understand
Java中的初始化。事实上，你可以做得更糟。如果你想了解
a new object oriented language, then study how it does object initialization and
一种新的面向对象的语言，然后研究它是如何进行对象初始化和
class initialization. Because essentially what happens in initialization is that all
类初始化。因为从本质上讲，在初始化中发生的是所有
the features of the language are going to be interacting and you have to explain
语言的特点将会是互动的，你必须解释
what all those interactions are and how they are sorted out in order to have a
所有这些交互是什么，以及如何对它们进行排序，以便
well-defined initialization procedure, alright. So, now let's talk about class
定义明确的初始化过程，好的。那么现在让我们来谈谈课堂
initialization. We won't talk about object initialization, we'll just talk about
初始化。我们不会讨论对象初始化，我们只会讨论
initializing classes. So, this is how the, the object that represents a class
正在初始化类。所以这就是，表示一个类的这个对象
actually gets initialized when that class is first brought into the program. And so,
实际上是在该类第一次被引入程序时初始化的。因此，
the first thing to know is that a class is initialized when a symbol in a class is
首先要知道的是，当类中的符号被初始化时，类就会被初始化
first used, okay, not when the class is loaded, alright? So, if you reference any
第一次使用，好的，不是在装入类的时候，好吗？因此，如果您引用任何
symbol in the class at the first time that happens that will cause the class to be
符号在类中的第一次出现，该符号将导致类被
initialized. And the reason for doing this is if you are going to have an error in
已初始化。这样做的原因是如果您将在
class initialization, th is will cause that error to happen in a predictable
类初始化，这将导致在可预测的
place. So, if you have an error and you run the, you, you have an error in class
地点。所以，如果你有一个错误，你运行，你，你在课堂上有一个错误
initialization if you run the program five times you know, that error will probably
初始化如果您运行该程序五次，该错误可能会
happen in the same place every time. So, it'll be repeatable and predictable where
每次都在同一个地方发生。因此，这将是可重复和可预测的
the error occurs. If instead we had, the error happened where you loaded the class
出现错误。如果相反，错误发生在您装入类的位置
at the time that you loaded the class, well, the class might be loaded at lots of
在您装入类的时候，这个类可能被装入了很多
different times. And, and, and so this, this, this error here the error in the
不同的时代。还有，还有，所以这个，这个，这个错误，这里的错误
initialization of the class would become non-deterministic if we didn't if we
如果我们不这样做，类的初始化将变得不确定
didn't delay the initialization until some deterministic point in the execution. So,
直到执行中的某个确定点才延迟初始化。所以,
now I'll discuss the procedure for initializing class objects in Java. And
现在我将讨论在Java中初始化类对象的过程。和
the first thing I should stress is that this idea of a class object is something
我要强调的第一件事是，类对象的概念是
that Java has that COOL does not have, I mentioned this on the previous slide. But
Java拥有酷炫没有的东西，我在上一张幻灯片中提到了这一点。但
just to be completely clear, what is a class object? A class object is just what
明确地说，什么是类对象？类对象就是
it sounds like, it is the object for a class. It represents a class. Okay, this
听起来好像，它是一个类的对象。它代表一个班级。好的，这个
is not an instance of the class. This is an object which is the class, okay. So,
不是该类的实例。这是一个对象，它是类，好的。所以,
this is an object which is the class, it has all the information about the class
这是一个对象，它是类，它包含有关类的所有信息
so, you know, it tells you what the type of the class is, what the fields of the
因此，您知道，它会告诉您类的类型、
class are, and everything else. So, this is used for introspection or reflection.
班级是，其他一切都是。所以，这是用来反省或反思的。
And it's necessary in Java because of features like dynamic loading. So, if, you
而且它在Java中是必要的，因为它具有动态加载等特性。所以如果你
know, if you want, if you dynamically load a class though you want to be able to use
要知道，如果您想要动态加载一个类，尽管您希望能够使用
that class, you have to have some way of querying what the, what kinds of methods
那个类，你必须有某种方式来查询什么，什么样的方法
and things the class has and that is what the class object is for. So, there is one
以及类所拥有的东西，这就是类对象的用途。所以，有一个
object, there is one class object for each class in Java, alright. So, when you load
对象，那么Java中的每个类都有一个类对象。所以，当你装入
a class, the first thing you have do is to initialize the class object. And how is
一个类，您要做的第一件事就是初始化类对象。那你还好吗？
that done? Well, we lock the class object for the class, alright. And if th at, if
做完了吗？好的，我们锁定类的类对象，好的。如果是这样的话，如果
that object is already locked by another thread, then we'll simply wait on the
该对象已被另一个线程锁定，那么我们只需等待
lock, okay. So, we will wait until somebody tells us that it's okay to
锁定，好的。所以，我们会等到有人告诉我们可以
proceed. Now once we obtain the lock on the class, we have to do a check to see if
开始吧。现在，一旦我们获得类的锁，我们就必须进行检查，看是否
the class is already being initialized, alright. So, and it could turn out that it
这个类已经在初始化了，好吧。所以，它可能会证明
is our thread, it is the same thread is already initializing the class. And how
是我们的线程，它是同一个线程已经在初始化类。以及如何
could that happen? Well, remember that a class can have fields of the same type.
这会发生吗？嗯，请记住，一个类可以有相同类型的字段。
So, I could have a class of class called X and then it could have a field of type X
因此，我可以有一个名为X的类，然后它可以有一个类型为X的字段
in it. And the way classes are going to be initialize if we're going to have to
在里面。如果我们必须这样做，那么类的初始化方式
initialize the class itself and then, and we're going to do that by recursively
初始化类本身，然后，我们将通过递归
initializing the classes for all the fields or at least making sure of the
初始化所有字段的类，或者至少确保
classes for all the fields are initialize. And if we have a recursive structure here
所有字段的类都已初始化。如果我们这里有一个递归结构
with the same class mention in a field as in a name, as the name of the enclosing
在字段中提及与在名称中提及的类相同的类，作为封闭的
class, then we will get the situation where the thread initializing the class
类，那么我们就会得到这样的情况：初始化类的线程
may attempt to initialize the same class again. So, if we discover that we're
可能会再次尝试初始化同一个类。所以，如果我们发现我们
already initializing this class, we simply release the lock and we turn. Now, another
已经初始化了这个类，我们只需释放锁，然后转向。现在，又来了一个
possibility is that the class is already initialized. So, if when we finally get
可能的情况是该类已经初始化。所以，如果当我们最终
the lock we discover that some other thread got in there and initialized the
我们发现某个其他线程进入了锁，并初始化了
class before we have a chance to., well, then there's nothing to do and we just
在我们有机会之前上课。嗯，那就没什么可做的了，我们只是
return normally, alright? Now, if neither one of these things is true, okay, if we
正常返回，好吗？现在，如果这两件事都不是真的，好吧，如果我们
get the lock and we discover that the class is not already initialized and that
获取锁后，我们发现类尚未初始化，并且
we're not already in the process of initializing the class, then we will mark
我们还没有在初始化类的过程中，那么我们将标记
the class to, to note the initialization is in progress by this thread, okay. So,
注意这个线程正在进行初始化的类，好的。所以,
we'll indicate, you know, this class is being initialized and that we are
我们会指出，您知道，这个类正在初始化，我们
initializing it and then we'll unlock the class. Alright, the next thing that
初始化它，然后我们将解锁该类。好的，接下来要做的就是
happens is we'll have to initialize the superclass and that will m ean initial,
发生的情况是我们必须初始化超类，这将是初始的，
and then we'll initialize all the fields in textual order. But because Java has
然后我们将按文本顺序初始化所有字段。而是因为Java有
what are called static and final fields we will initialize those first, okay. So,
所谓的静电和最终字段，我们会先初始化它们，好的。所以,
static final fields will get initialized before any other fields in textual order.
静电最终字段将在文本顺序中的任何其他字段之前初始化。
And, of course, we have to give every field of default value before
当然，在此之前，我们必须给出每个字段的默认值
initialization just as in COOL. So, this step, step five is very similar to what
初始化就像在Cool中一样。所以这一步，第五步跟什么很相似
goes on in COOL. Now if there's an error during the initialization, so some part of
在凉爽中进行。现在，如果在初始化过程中出现错误，那么
the initialization throws an exception, then we're going to mark the class as
初始化抛出异常，然后我们将该类标记为
erroneous, okay, we're going to mark this class as no good and can't be used and,
错误，好的，我们要把这门课标记为不好，不能用，
and that's the best we can do. So, if there's an exception during
这是我们能做的最好的了。因此，如果在此过程中出现异常
initialization, we just have to give up on that class. And so it gets a special mark
初始化时，我们只能放弃那个类。所以它会有一个特殊的标记
on it saying that it's erroneous. And, if there are no errors if we succeed in
说这是错误的。如果没有错误，如果我们成功地
initializing the class and with and without any errors, then we're going to
初始化类，并且有或没有任何错误，然后我们将
lock the class again. We will label the class as initialized, alright? And then
再次锁定班级。我们会将类标记为已初始化，好吗？然后
we'll notify the threads that are waiting on the class object. So. Anybody who was
我们将通知正在等待类对象的线程。所以。任何曾经是
locked waiting on the class object will now be alerted that the object is, is
正在等待类对象的锁定现在将被警告该对象是、是
ready and then we'll unlock the class. Okay, and so that's a rough outline of how
准备好了，然后我们就解锁班级。好的，这就是粗略的描述
class initialization in Java works. I skipped over a few things and
Java中的类初始化工作正常。我略过了几件事
oversimplified it a bit. So, this isn't the complete description but these are the
有点过于简单化了。所以，这不是完整的描述，但这些是
main points and they, and they illustrate how the various features of the language
要点和它们，它们说明了语言的各种特征
have to interact. So, you have to worry about concurrency, you have to worry about
必须互动。所以，你必须担心并发性，你必须担心
exceptions, you have to worry about static and final fields, you have to worry about
例外，你要担心静电和Final字段，你要担心
inheritance. I mean, all these things have to be dealt with together in the design of
继承。我的意思是，所有这些事情都必须在设计的时候一起处理
a single algorithm to do class initialization. Stepping back for a moment
执行类初始化的单一算法。后退片刻
this discussion of class initialization in Java illustrates a general point about
关于Java中的类初始化的讨论说明了关于
designing complex systems. So, in any system with a certain number of featu res
设计复杂的系统。因此，在任何具有一定数量的功能的系统中
and every system is going to have some number of features, let's call it N,
每个系统都会有一些功能，让我们称它为N，
because you want to provide some functionality, obviously the thing the
因为您想要提供一些功能，显然
system's suppose to d so its going to have features to do those things. But as you
系统应该是d，所以它会有功能来做这些事情。但是当你
add features, you get lots of interactions, potential interactions
添加功能，您将获得大量交互、潜在交互
between the features and if we think about, even just the pairwise
在这些特征之间，如果我们想一想，即使是成对的
interactions. If I have N features, then I'll have, I don't know, about N^2
互动。如果我有N个特征，那么我就会有，我不知道，大约N^2
pairwise feature interactions. And the point there, of course, is that as I add
成对功能交互。当然，这里的重点是，正如我补充的那样
features the number of possible interactions grows super linearly in the
功能中，可能的交互数量呈超线性增长。
number of features, I mean, it grows much more quickly than the number of features.
功能的数量，我的意思是，它的增长速度远远快于功能的数量。
And so, adding the next feature, you're going to have to consider all of the
因此，添加下一个功能时，您将不得不考虑所有
previous features that you already have in the system and how this new feature
系统中已有的以前功能，以及此新功能如何
affects them, and this is why it becomes very difficult to extend or build systems
影响它们，这就是为什么扩展或构建系统变得非常困难的原因
that have a lot of features, alright. And this is just the pairwise features. These
有很多特色的，好吧。这只是两两配对的特征。这些
are just, this is just considering pairwise interactions between one feature
只是，这只是考虑了一个要素之间的成对交互
and another. If I have to start worrying about subsets of features, I'm thinking
再来一次。如果我必须开始担心功能的子集，我在想
about how all possible subsets of features might interact with each other, well then,
关于所有可能的特征子集如何彼此交互，那么，
this step, this number of, of potential interactions will grow not just it will
这一步，这一潜在互动的数量将会增长，而不仅仅是
grow, in fact, exponentially. So, it'd be, you know, way more than quadratic. And the
事实上，成倍增长。所以，它会，你知道，远远超过二次。以及
bottom line here is that big, feature-full systems are hard to understand. You know,
这里的底线是，功能齐全的大型系统很难理解。你知道,
this is you know, a general lesson in Computer Science and any kind of
你知道，这是一堂关于计算机科学的普通课，以及任何形式的
discipline that wants to design complex systems and, and this lesson applies to
想要设计复杂系统的学科，本课适用于
programming languages. It applies to every other kind of software system that you
编程语言。它适用于您所使用的所有其他类型的软件系统
might want to build. But, and somehow it has a particular force in programming
可能会想要建造。但是，不知何故，它在编程方面有一种特殊的力量
languages because these interactions between the features, you know, these are
语言，因为这些功能之间的交互，你知道，这些是
the features of the programming language, they happen at a very fine grain. And
编程语言的特点，它们发生在非常细微的粒度上。和
these things can be, really can b e composed arbitrarily and so you really do
这些东西可以，真的可以任意组合，所以你真的这样做了
have to work out in language design, you know, what all the interactions are in
我必须在语言设计中工作，你知道，所有的交互都包含在
order to have a language that people, that programmers can actually understand and
为了拥有一种人们、程序员能够真正理解的语言，
use productively. Alright? And that really I think is the big, big idea that, one of
高效使用。好吗？我真的认为这是一个很大很大的想法，
the big ideas that we've talked about throughout the course. And, and I hope one
我们在整个课程中谈到的重要思想。而且，我希望能有一个
of the things that you would take away from this lecture at least in particular.
你会从这堂课中学到的东西，至少是特别的。
So, to summarize and to conclude our discussion of Java, I think Java is a, is
因此，总结和总结我们对Java的讨论，我认为Java是一种
a well-done language. By production standards, it is extremely well-done. So,
一种做得很好的语言。按照生产标准，这道菜做得非常好。所以,
it's one of the best designed and best specified languages that's in, in use
它是目前正在使用的设计最好、指定最好的语言之一
today. It brought several important ideas into the main stream. So, when it was new
今天。它把几个重要的思想带入主流。所以，当它是新的时候
it brought ideas that had been around for a long time but had not found their way
它带来的想法已经存在很长一段时间了，但一直没有找到方向。
into a production language that was very, very widely used and in particular, Java
转换成一种非常、非常广泛使用的生产语言，特别是Java
was the first language to be very widely used in, in commercial settings. They had
是第一种在商业环境中被广泛使用的语言。他们有
strong sets of typing there that had real guarantees they were, you know, provided
强大的打字套装在那里有真正的保证，你知道，它们提供了
by the type-system and also there was a manage language and had a garbage
通过类型系统，还有一个托管语言和一个垃圾
collected memory. But that doesn't mean it's perfect. And it, and Java also
收集的内存。但这并不意味着它是完美的。还有它，还有Java也
includes some features that, at the time that it was designed, that we didn't fully
包括一些功能，在设计它的时候，我们没有完全
understand and I would say, you know, that this are probably the rough areas where
理解，我想说，你知道，这可能是最艰难的领域
there's still some roughness in the, in, in the Java design. So, things like the
在Java设计中，仍有一些粗糙之处。所以，像这样的东西
way the memory semantics work in the presence of concurrency, you know,
内存语义在并发性存在的情况下工作的方式，你知道，
probably still has most people would agree I think, you now, has some problems and
可能还有很多人会同意我觉得，你现在，有一些问题，
some, some little gray areas that as a program, you probably want to stay out of.
一些，一些小的灰色地带，作为一个程序，你可能想置身事外。
And the other thing is that Java has a lot of features. And as I said before when you
另一件事是Java有很多特性。就像我之前说的，当你
have a lot of features, you're going to have even more feature interactions and
有很多功能，您将会有更多的功能交互
that leads to complexity that becomes difficult to manage.
这导致复杂性变得难以管理。